LOGAN DAVIS

Phone: (479) 530-4482 Logan@LoganRDavis.com 3100 Hearthstone Dr. Fayetteville, AR 72764

I am a Fluent programmer and despite my University courses, I have learned most of what I know from experience in projects and online resources. I am a quick learner and focused worker who has to stay busy. I have experience managing people and excel at delegation and time management. I enjoy new challenges and branching out to new technologies.

EDUCATION

University of Arkansas		
Bachelor's degree	Computer Science	2016-2019
Minor	Information Systems	2019-2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder & Chief Technology Officer

Labor Saver Solutions

March 2019 - Present

I Started my own company as the sole software and hardware engineer. To summarize the company, I develop, and my partner sells technology devices and services such as wireless RF call buttons and temperature sensors. We then provide a web app that allows for analysis and setup of email and texting notifications based on user preferences. As the sole technology provider, I have experience developing database schemas, restful APIs, microcontroller processes, multithreaded hub controller units, and frontend user experiences. I designed PCB schematics using Eagle CAD and worked with foreign manufacturers to acquire parts. I have also worked with external services such as SendGrid, Twilio, and Google Cloud to provide an all-encompassing service.

www.LaborSaver.Solutions

Mechanic Manager

Lokomotion Family Fun Park

March 2016 - August 2019

domain classes and structures, handling customers, SAP ERP software.

My first job led from a simple attendant position to a managerial mechanical one. I received on the job training as well as Honda TACS training in order to learn small engine and go kart repair. I can completely disassemble a small engine or go kart and reassemble. I have also acquired a skill for electrical wiring and system diagnosis. This position allowed me to become a manager overseeing procurement of parts, budget management, managing apprentice mechanics, as well as making impactful operation decisions.

SKILL BASE

Software Development Background:	JavaScript Python C++ Java C# SQL NOSQL
	Google Cloud Node.js jQuery React Corvid
	Visual Studio Code PyCharm Visual Studio Android Studio Eclipse
Additionally skilled in:	
	Low power/resource software development, creating server-side APIs, management/delegation, training, system diagnoses, budgeting, system design.
Experience with:	
-	Creating system diagrams, designing top level technology solutions, building